A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, general correspondence, RG 2, 1947-1951 FA759
Rockefeller Archive Center
- General Correspondence, 1950
  - Virginia, 1950; 1950/252
    - Virginia - Humanities and Arts, 1950; 1950/252.R
      - Virginia, 1950 (Box 492, Folder 3295)
  - Washington, 1950; 1950/253
    - Washington (Box 492, Folder 3296)
    - Washington - Humanities and Arts, 1950; 1950/253.R
      - Washington, 1950 (Box 492, Folder 3296)
  - Wisconsin, 1950; 1950/255
    - Wisconsin, 1950 (Box 492, Folder 3296)
  - South America, 1950; 1950/300
    - South America - Administration, 1950 (Box 492, Folder 3297)
    - South America, 1950 (Box 493, Folder 3298)
    - South America - Medical Sciences, 1950; 1950/300.A
      - South America, 1950 (Box 493, Folder 3299)
    - South America - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1950; 1950/300.D
      - South America, 1950 (Box 493, Folder 3299)
    - South America - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1950; 1950/300.E
      - South America, 1950 (Box 493, Folder 3299)
    - South America - Social Sciences, 1950; 1950/300.S
      - South America, 1950 (Box 493, Folder 3299)
  - Argentina, 1950; 1950/301
    - Argentina, 1950 (Box 493, Folder 3300)
    - Argentina - Nursing, 1950; 1950/301.C
      - Argentina, 1950 (Box 493, Folder 3300)
    - Argentina - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1950; 1950/301.D
      - Argentina, 1950 (Box 493, Folder 3300)
  - Bolivia, 1950; 1950/303
    - Bolivia, 1950 (Box 493, Folder 3300)
    - Bolivia - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1950; 1950/303.D
      - Bolivia, 1950 (Box 493, Folder 3300)
  - Brazil, 1950; 1950/305
    - Brazil - (A-Z), 1950 (Box 493, Folder 3301)
    - Brazil - (A-Z), 1950 (Box 493, Folder 3302)
    - Brazil - (A-Z), 1950 (Box 493, Folder 3303)
    - Brazil - Medical Sciences, 1950; 1950/305.A
      - Brazil, 1950 (Box 493, Folder 3304)
    - Brazil - Nursing, 1950; 1950/305.C
      - Brazil, 1950 (Box 493, Folder 3304)
    - Brazil - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1950; 1950/305.D
      - Brazil, 1950 (Box 493, Folder 3304)
    - Brazil - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1950; 1950/305.E
      - Brazil, 1950 (Box 493, Folder 3304)
    - Brazil - Malaria, 1950; 1950/305.I
      - Brazil, 1950 (Box 494, Folder 3305)
    - Brazil - Yellow Fever, 1950; 1950/305.O
      - Brazil, 1950 (Box 494, Folder 3306)
    - Brazil - Humanities and Arts, 1950; 1950/305.R
      - Brazil, 1950 (Box 494, Folder 3306)
    - Brazil - Tuberculosis, 1950; 1950/305.T
      - Brazil, 1950 (Box 494, Folder 3306)
  - Chile, 1950; 1950/309
    - Chile, 1950 (Box 494, Folder 3307)
    - Chile - Medical Sciences, 1950; 1950/309.A
      - Chile, 1950 (Box 494, Folder 3307)
    - Chile - Nursing, 1950; 1950/309.C
      - Chile, 1950 (Box 494, Folder 3307)
    - Chile - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1950; 1950/309.D
      - Chile, 1950 (Box 494, Folder 3307)
    - Chile - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1950; 1950/309.E
      - Chile, 1950 (Box 494, Folder 3307)
  - Colombia, 1950; 1950/311
    - Colombia - (A-N), 1950 (Box 494, Folder 3308)
    - Colombia - (O-Z), 1950 (Box 494, Folder 3309)
    - Colombia - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1950; 1950/311.D
      - Colombia, 1950 (Box 494, Folder 3310)
    - Colombia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1950; 1950/311.E
      - Colombia, 1950 (Box 494, Folder 3310)
  - Costa Rica, 1950; 1950/313
    - Costa Rica, 1950 (Box 494, Folder 3311)
    - Costa Rica - Nursing, 1950; 1950/313.C
      - Costa Rica, 1950 (Box 494, Folder 3311)
  - Cuba, 1950; 1950/315
    - Cuba, 1950 (Box 494, Folder 3311)
    - Cuba - Humanities and Arts, 1950; 1950/315.R
      - Cuba, 1950 (Box 494, Folder 3311)
  - Ecuador, 1950; 1950/317
    - Ecuador, 1950 (Box 494, Folder 3311)
  - Guatemala, 1950; 1950/319
    - Guatemala, 1950 (Box 494, Folder 3311)
    - Guatemala - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1950; 1950/319.D
      - Guatemala, 1950 (Box 494, Folder 3311)
    - Guatemala - Humanities and Arts, 1950; 1950/319.R
      - Guatemala, 1950 (Box 494, Folder 3311)
  - Haiti, 1950; 1950/320
    - Haiti, 1950 (Box 494, Folder 3311)
  - Honduras, 1950; 1950/321
    - Honduras, 1950 (Box 494, Folder 3311)
  - Mexico, 1950; 1950/323
    - Mexico - Administration, 1950 (Box 495, Folder 3312)
    - Mexico, 1950 (Box 495, Folder 3313)
    - Mexico - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1950; 1950/323.E
      - Mexico, 1950 (Box 495, Folder 3313)
    - Mexico - Humanities and Arts, 1950; 1950/323.R
      - Mexico, 1950 (Box 495, Folder 3313)
  - Nicaragua, 1950; 1950/325
    - Nicaragua, 1950 (Box 495, Folder 3314)
    - Nicaragua - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1950; 1950/325.D
      - Nicaragua, 1950 (Box 495, Folder 3314)
  - Panama, 1950; 1950/327
    - Panama, 1950 (Box 495, Folder 3314)
    - Panama - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1950; 1950/327.E
      - Panama, 1950 (Box 495, Folder 3314)
    - Panama - Malaria, 1950; 1950/327.I
      - Panama, 1950 (Box 495, Folder 3314)
    - Panama - Yellow Fever, 1950; 1950/327.O
      - Panama, 1950 (Box 495, Folder 3314)
    - Panama - Humanities and Arts, 1950; 1950/327.R
      - Panama, 1950 (Box 495, Folder 3314)
  - Peru, 1950; 1950/331
    - Peru, 1950 (Box 495, Folder 3314)
    - Peru - Medical Sciences, 1950; 1950/331.A
      - Peru, 1950 (Box 495, Folder 3314)
    - Peru - Nursing, 1950; 1950/331.C
      - Peru, 1950 (Box 495, Folder 3314)
    - Peru - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1950; 1950/331.D
      - Peru, 1950 (Box 495, Folder 3314)
    - Peru - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1950; 1950/331.E
      - Peru, 1950 (Box 495, Folder 3314)
  - El Salvador, 1950; 1950/333
    - El Salvador, 1950 (Box 495, Folder 3315)
  - Dominican Republic, 1950; 1950/335
    - Dominican Republic, 1950 (Box 495, Folder 3315)
    - Dominican Republic - Malaria, 1950; 1950/335.I
      - Dominican Republic, 1950 (Box 495, Folder 3315)
  - Uruguay, 1950; 1950/337
    - Uruguay, 1950 (Box 495, Folder 3315)
    - Uruguay - Medical Sciences, 1950; 1950/337.A
      - Uruguay, 1950 (Box 495, Folder 3315)
    - Uruguay - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1950; 1950/337.E
      - Uruguay, 1950 (Box 495, Folder 3315)
  - Venezeula, 1950; 1950/339
    - Venezuela, 1950 (Box 495, Folder 3316)
    - Venezeula - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1950; 1950/339.E
      - Venezuela, 1950 (Box 495, Folder 3317)
    - Venezeula - Yellow Fever, 1950; 1950/339.O
      - Venezuela, 1950 (Box 495, Folder 3317)
  - Great Britain, 1950; 1950/400
    - Great Britain, 1950 (Box 496, Folder 3318)
  - England, 1950; 1950/401
    - England - (A-H), 1950 (Box 496, Folder 3318)
    - England - Medical Sciences, 1950; 1950/401.A
      - England, 1950 (Box 496, Folder 3322)
    - England - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1950; 1950/401.D
      - England, 1950 (Box 496, Folder 3322)
    - England - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1950; 1950/401.E
      - England, 1950 (Box 496, Folder 3322)
    - England - Public Health Education, 1950; 1950/401.L
      - England, 1950 (Box 496, Folder 3322)
    - England - Humanities and Arts, 1950; 1950/401.R
      - England, 1950 (Box 496, Folder 3322)
    - England - Social Sciences, 1950; 1950/401.S
      - England, 1950 (Box 496, Folder 3322)
  - Ireland, 1950; 1950/403
    - Ireland, 1950 (Box 496, Folder 3323)
    - Ireland - Humanities and Arts, 1950; 1950/403.R
      - Ireland, 1950 (Box 496, Folder 3323)
  - Scotland, 1950; 1950/405
    - Scotland, 1950 (Box 496, Folder 3323)
    - Scotland - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1950; 1950/405.E
      - Scotland, 1950 (Box 496, Folder 3323)
    - Scotland - Social Sciences, 1950; 1950/405.S
      - Scotland, 1950 (Box 496, Folder 3323)
  - Wales, 1950; 1950/407
    - Wales, 1950 (Box 496, Folder 3323)
  - Australia, 1950; 1950/410
    - Australia - (A-T), 1950 (Box 497, Folder 3324)
    - Australia - (U-Z), 1950 (Box 497, Folder 3325)
    - Australia - Medical Sciences, 1950; 1950/410.A
      - Australia, 1950 (Box 497, Folder 3325)
    - Australia - Nursing, 1950; 1950/410.C
      - Australia, 1950 (Box 497, Folder 3325)
    - Australia - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1950; 1950/410.D
      - Australia, 1950 (Box 497, Folder 3325)
    - Australia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1950; 1950/410.E
      - Australia, 1950 (Box 497, Folder 3325)
    - Australia - Humanities and Arts, 1950; 1950/410.R
      - Australia, 1950 (Box 497, Folder 3325)
    - Australia - Social Sciences, 1950; 1950/410.S
      - Australia, 1950 (Box 497, Folder 3325)
  - New Zealand, 1950; 1950/418
    - New Zealand, 1950 (Box 497, Folder 3326)
    - New Zealand - Medical Sciences, 1950; 1950/418.A
      - New Zealand, 1950 (Box 497, Folder 3326)
  - Caribbean, 1950; 1950/420
    - Caribbean Region, 1950 (Box 497, Folder 3326)
    - Caribbean Region, 1950 (Box 497, Folder 3327)
  - Guyana, 1950; 1950/423
    - Guiana, 1950 (Box 497, Folder 3327)
  - Canada, 1950; 1950/427
    - Canada - Administration, 1950 (Box 497, Folder 3328)
    - Canada - (A-Z), 1950 (Box 497, Folder 3329)
    - Canada - (A-Z), 1950 (Box 497, Folder 3330)
    - Canada - University (A-Z), 1950 (Box 498, Folder 3331)
    - Canada - Medical Sciences, 1950; 1950/427.A
      - Canada, 1950 (Box 498, Folder 3331)
    - Canada - Nursing, 1950; 1950/427.C
      - Canada, 1950 (Box 498, Folder 3331)
    - Canada - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1950; 1950/427.E
      - Canada, 1950 (Box 498, Folder 3331)
    - Canada - Humanities and Arts, 1950; 1950/427.R
      - Canada, 1950 (Box 498, Folder 3332)
    - Canada - Social Sciences, 1950; 1950/427.S
      - Canada, 1950 (Box 498, Folder 3332)
  - Jamaica, 1950; 1950/437
    - Jamaica, 1950 (Box 498, Folder 3333)
    - Jamaica - Medical Sciences, 1950; 1950/437.A
      - Jamaica, 1950 (Box 498, Folder 3333)
    - Jamaica - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1950; 1950/437.E
      - Jamaica, 1950 (Box 498, Folder 3333)
  - Trinidad, 1950; 1950/451
    - Trinidad, 1950 (Box 498, Folder 3333)
  - Sri Lanka, 1950; 1950/462
    - Sri Lanka, 1950 (Box 498, Folder 3333)
    - Sri Lanka - Nursing, 1950; 1950/462.C
      - Sri Lanka, 1950 (Box 498, Folder 3333)
    - Sri Lanka - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1950; 1950/462.E
      - Sri Lanka, 1950 (Box 498, Folder 3333)
    - Sri Lanka - Malaria, 1950; 1950/462.I
      - Sri Lanka, 1950 (Box 498, Folder 3333)
  - Hong Kong, 1950; 1950/463
    Hong Kong
    - Hong Kong, 1950 (Box 498, Folder 3333)
  - India, 1950; 1950/464
    - India - (A-Z), 1950 (Box 498, Folder 3334)
    - India - (A-Z), 1950 (Box 498, Folder 3335)
    - India - Medical Sciences, 1950; 1950/464.A
      - India, 1950 (Box 498, Folder 3336)
    - India - Nursing, 1950; 1950/464.C
      - India, 1950 (Box 498, Folder 3336)
    - India - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1950; 1950/464.E
      - India, 1950 (Box 498, Folder 3336)
    - India - Malaria, 1950; 1950/464.I
      - India, 1950 (Box 498, Folder 3336)
    - India - Public Health Demonstrations, 1950; 1950/464.J
      - India, 1950 (Box 498, Folder 3336)
    - India - Humanities and Arts, 1950; 1950/464.R
      - India, 1950 (Box 498, Folder 3336)
    - India - Social Sciences, 1950; 1950/464.S
      - India, 1950 (Box 498, Folder 3336)
  - Pakistan, 1950; 1950/465
    - Pakistan, 1950 (Box 499, Folder 3337)
    - Pakistan - Nursing, 1950; 1950/465.C
      - Pakistan, 1950 (Box 499, Folder 3337)
    - Pakistan - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1950; 1950/465.E
      - Pakistan, 1950 (Box 499, Folder 3337)
    - Pakistan - Social Sciences, 1950; 1950/465.S
      - Pakistan, 1950 (Box 499, Folder 3337)
  - Burma, 1950; 1950/468
    - Burma, 1950 (Box 499, Folder 3337)
  - Iraq, 1950; 1950/470
    - Iraq, 1950 (Box 499, Folder 3337)
    - Iraq - Nursing, 1950; 1950/470.C
      - Iraq, 1950 (Box 499, Folder 3337)
    - Iraq - Malaria, 1950; 1950/470.I
      - Iraq, 1950 (Box 499, Folder 3337)
  - New Guinea, 1950; 1950/472
    Papua New Guinea
    - New Guinea, 1950 (Box 499, Folder 3337)
  - Malayasia, 1950; 1950/473
    - Malaysia, 1950 (Box 499, Folder 3337)
    - Malayasia - Medical Sciences, 1950; 1950/473.A
      - Malaysia, 1950 (Box 499, Folder 3337)
  - Africa, 1950; 1950/475
    - Africa, 1950 (Box 499, Folder 3338)
    - Africa - Medical Sciences, 1950; 1950/475.A
      - Africa, 1950 (Box 499, Folder 3338)
      - MOR-1 Morison, Robert S. "Diary of a Trip to Syria and Africa", 1950 (Box 563, Folder 3838)
    - Africa - Social Sciences, 1950; 1950/475.S
      - Africa, 1950 (Box 499, Folder 3338)
  - East Africa Region, 1950; 1950/477
    Africa, East
    - East Africa, 1950 (Box 499, Folder 3338)
    - East Africa Region - Medical Sciences, 1950; 1950/477.A
      - East Africa, 1950 (Box 499, Folder 3338)
    - East Africa Region - Nursing, 1950; 1950/477.C
      - East Africa, 1950 (Box 499, Folder 3338)
    - East Africa Region - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1950; 1950/477.E
      - East Africa, 1950 (Box 499, Folder 3338)
  - Egypt, 1950; 1950/485
    - Egypt - Administration, 1950 (Box 499, Folder 3339)
    - Egypt, 1950 (Box 499, Folder 3340)
    - Egypt - Medical Sciences, 1950; 1950/485.A
      - Egypt, 1950 (Box 499, Folder 3340)
    - Egypt - Nursing, 1950; 1950/485.C
      - Egypt, 1950 (Box 499, Folder 3340)
    - Egypt - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1950; 1950/485.E
      - Egypt, 1950 (Box 499, Folder 3340)
    - Egypt - Public Health Demonstrations, 1950; 1950/485.J
      - Egypt, 1950 (Box 499, Folder 3340)
  - South Africa, 1950; 1950/487
    - South Africa, 1950 (Box 499, Folder 3341)
    - South Africa - Medical Sciences, 1950; 1950/487.A
      - South Africa, 1950 (Box 499, Folder 3342)
    - South Africa - Nursing, 1950; 1950/487.C
      - South Africa, 1950 (Box 499, Folder 3342)
    - South Africa - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1950; 1950/487.E
      - South Africa, 1950 (Box 499, Folder 3342)
  - West Africa, 1950; 1950/495
    - West Africa, 1950 (Box 500, Folder 3343)
    - West Africa - Medical Sciences, 1950; 1950/495.A
      - West Africa, 1950 (Box 500, Folder 3343)
  - France, 1950; 1950/500
    - France - (A-Z), 1950 (Box 500, Folder 3344)
    - France - (A-Z), 1950 (Box 500, Folder 3345)
    - France - (A-Z), 1950 (Box 500, Folder 3346)
    - France - Medical Sciences, 1950; 1950/500.A
      - France, 1950 (Box 500, Folder 3347)
    - France - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1950; 1950/500.D
      - France, 1950 (Box 500, Folder 3347)
    - France - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1950; 1950/500.E
      - France, 1950 (Box 500, Folder 3347)
    - France - Humanities and Arts, 1950; 1950/500.R
      - France, 1950 (Box 500, Folder 3347)
    - France - Social Services, 1950; 1950/500.S
      - France, 1950 (Box 500, Folder 3347)
  - Corsica, 1950; 1950/502
    Corsica
    - Corsica - Malaria, 1950; 1950/502.I
      - Corsica, 1950 (Box 500, Folder 3347)
  - Vietnam, 1950; 1950/509
    - Vietnam, 1950 (Box 500, Folder 3347)
  - Asia, 1950; 1950/600
    - Asia, 1950 (Box 500, Folder 3347)
    - Asia - Social Sciences, 1950; 1950/600.S
      - Asia, 1950 (Box 500, Folder 3347)
      - Asia - Evans, Roger F. - Diary South and Southeast Asia, September-December 1950 (Box 500, Folder 3348)
  - China, 1950; 1950/601
    - China, 1950 (Box 501, Folder 3349)
    - China - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1950; 1950/601.E
      - China, 1950 (Box 501, Folder 3349)
    - China - Social Services, 1950; 1950/601.S
      - China, 1950 (Box 501, Folder 3349)
  - Taiwan, 1950; 1950/605
    - Taiwan, 1950 (Box 501, Folder 3350)
    - Taiwan - Medical Sciences, 1950; 1950/605.A
      - Taiwan, 1950 (Box 501, Folder 3350)
    - Taiwan - Nursing, 1950; 1950/605.C
      - Taiwan, 1950 (Box 501, Folder 3350)
  - Japan, 1950; 1950/609
    - Japan - Administration - (A-Ins), 1950 (Box 501, Folder 3351)
    - Japan - International Christian - University, 1950 (Box 501, Folder 3352)
    - Japan - (Int-Oz), 1950 (Box 501, Folder 3353)
    - Japan - (P-Z), 1950 (Box 501, Folder 3354)
    - Japan - Medical Sciences, 1950; 1950/609.A
      - Japan, 1950 (Box 501, Folder 3355)
    - Japan - Nursing, 1950; 1950/609.C
      - Japan, 1950 (Box 501, Folder 3355)
    - Japan - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1950; 1950/609.E
      - Japan, 1950 (Box 501, Folder 3355)
    - Japan - Humanities and Arts, 1950; 1950/609.R
      - Japan, 1950 (Box 501, Folder 3355)
    - Japan - Social Services, 1950; 1950/609.S
      - Japan, 1950 (Box 501, Folder 3355)
  - Korea, 1950; 1950/613
    - Korea, 1950 (Box 502, Folder 3357)
    - Korea - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1950; 1950/613.E
      - Korea, 1950 (Box 502, Folder 3357)
    - Korea - Humanities and Arts, 1950; 1950/613.R
      - Korea, 1950 (Box 502, Folder 3357)
  - Thailand, 1950; 1950/617
    - Thailand, 1950 (Box 502, Folder 3356)
    - Thailand - Medical Sciences, 1950; 1950/617.A
      - Thailand, 1950 (Box 502, Folder 3356)
    - Thailand - Humanities and Arts, 1950; 1950/617.R
      - Thailand, 1950 (Box 502, Folder 3356)
  - Southeast Asia, 1950; 1950/625
    - Southeast Asia, 1950 (Box 502, Folder 3356)
  - Holland, 1950; 1950/650
    - Netherlands, 1950 (Box 502, Folder 3358)
    - Holland - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1950; 1950/650.E
      - Netherlands, 1950 (Box 502, Folder 3359)
    - Holland - Humanities and Arts, 1950; 1950/650.R
      - Netherlands, 1950 (Box 502, Folder 3359)
    - Holland - Social Services, 1950; 1950/650.S
      - Netherlands, 1950 (Box 502, Folder 3359)
  - Indonesia, 1950; 1950/652
    - Indonesia, 1950 (Box 502, Folder 3359)
    - Indonesia - Medical Services, 1950; 1950/652.A
      - Indonesia, 1950 (Box 502, Folder 3359)
    - Indonesia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1950; 1950/652.E
      - Indonesia, 1950 (Box 502, Folder 3359)
    - Indonesia - Humanities and Arts, 1950; 1950/652.R
      - Indonesia, 1950 (Box 502, Folder 3359)
  - Java, 1950; 1950/655
    - Java, 1950 (Box 502, Folder 3359)
  - Europe, 1950; 1950/700
    - Europe - Struthers, Robert R., 1950 (Box 502, Folder 3360)
    - Europe - Medical Sciences, 1950; 1950/700.A
      - Europe - Bachmeyer, Arthur C. - "Survey of European Medical Schools", 1950 (Box 502, Folder 3361)
    - Europe - Social Sciences, 1950; 1950/700.S
      - Europe - Buchanan, Norman S. - "Marginalia on European Program", 1950 (Box 502, Folder 3361)
      - Europe - Mosely, Philip E. - "European Trip Notes", 1950 (Box 502, Folder 3362)
  - Austria, 1950; 1950/705
    - Austria, 1950 (Box 503, Folder 3363)
    - Austria - Medical Sciences, 1950; 1950/705.A
      - Austria, 1950 (Box 503, Folder 3363)
    - Austria - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1950; 1950/705.D
      - Austria, 1950 (Box 503, Folder 3363)
    - Austria - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1950; 1950/705.E
      - Austria, 1950 (Box 503, Folder 3363)
    - Austria - Humanities and Arts, 1950; 1950/705.R
      - Austria, 1950 (Box 503, Folder 3363)
    - Austria - Social Services, 1950; 1950/705.S
      - Austria, 1950 (Box 503, Folder 3363)
  - Belgium, 1950; 1950/707
    - Belgium, 1950 (Box 503, Folder 3364)
    - Belgium - Medical Sciences, 1950; 1950/707.A
      - Belgium, 1950 (Box 503, Folder 3364)
    - Belgium - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1950; 1950/707.E
      - Belgium, 1950 (Box 503, Folder 3364)
    - Belgium - Social Services, 1950; 1950/707.S
      - Belgium, 1950 (Box 503, Folder 3364)
  - Yugoslavia, 1950; 1950/710
    - Yugoslavia, 1950 (Box 503, Folder 3365)
    - Yugoslavia - Medical Sciences, 1950; 1950/710.A
      - Yugoslavia, 1950 (Box 503, Folder 3365)
    - Yugoslavia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1950; 1950/710.E
      - Yugoslavia, 1950 (Box 503, Folder 3365)
  - Bulgaria, 1950; 1950/711
    - Bulgaria, 1950 (Box 503, Folder 3365)
  - Czechoslovakia, 1950; 1950/712
    - Czechoslovakia, 1950 (Box 503, Folder 3365)
  - Denmark, 1950; 1950/713
    - Denmark, 1950 (Box 503, Folder 3366)
    - Denmark - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1950; 1950/713.D
      - Denmark, 1950 (Box 503, Folder 3366)
    - Denmark - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1950; 1950/713.E
      - Denmark, 1950 (Box 503, Folder 3366)
    - Denmark - Humanities and Arts, 1950; 1950/713.R
      - Denmark, 1950 (Box 503, Folder 3366)
  - Iceland, 1950; 1950/715
    - Iceland, 1950 (Box 503, Folder 3366)
  - Scandinavia, 1950; 1950/716
    - Scandinavia, 1950 (Box 503, Folder 3366)
  - Germany, 1950; 1950/717
    - Germany, 1950 (Box 503, Folder 3367)
    - Germany - (A-U), 1950 (Box 503, Folder 3368)
    - Germany - (A-U), 1950 (Box 503, Folder 3369)
    - Germany - University - (A-Z), 1950 (Box 504, Folder 3370)
    - Germany - (V-Z), 1950 (Box 504, Folder 3371)
    - Germany - Medical Services, 1950; 1950/717.A
      - Germany, 1950 (Box 504, Folder 3371)
    - Germany - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1950; 1950/717.D
      - Germany, 1950 (Box 504, Folder 3371)
    - Germany - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1950; 1950/717.E
      - Germany, 1950 (Box 504, Folder 3371)
    - Germany - Humanities and Arts, 1950; 1950/717.R
      - Germany, 1950 (Box 504, Folder 3371)
    - Germany - Social Services, 1950; 1950/717.S
      - Germany, 1950 (Box 504, Folder 3371)
  - Angaur Island, 1950; 1950/741
    - Angaur Island, 1950 (Box 504, Folder 3372)
  - Greece, 1950; 1950/749
    - Greece, 1950 (Box 504, Folder 3372)
    - Greece - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1950; 1950/749.E
      - Greece, 1950 (Box 504, Folder 3372)
    - Greece - Humanities and Arts, 1950; 1950/749.R
      - Greece, 1950 (Box 504, Folder 3372)
  - Hungary, 1950; 1950/750
    - Hungary, 1950 (Box 504, Folder 3372)
  - Italy, 1950; 1950/751
    - Italy, 1950 (Box 504, Folder 3373)
    - Italy - Medical Services, 1950; 1950/751.A
      - Italy, 1950 (Box 504, Folder 3374)
    - Italy - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1950; 1950/751.D
      - Italy, 1950 (Box 504, Folder 3374)
    - Italy - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1950; 1950/751.E
      - Italy, 1950 (Box 504, Folder 3374)
    - Italy - Social Sciences, 1950; 1950/751.S
      - Italy, 1950 (Box 504, Folder 3374)
  - Luxembourg, 1950; 1950/760
    - Luxembourg, 1950 (Box 504, Folder 3374)
  - Norway, 1950; 1950/767
    - Norway, 1950 (Box 504, Folder 3375)
    - Norway - Medical Sciences, 1950; 1950/767.A
      - Norway, 1950 (Box 504, Folder 3375)
    - Norway - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1950; 1950/767.E
      - Norway, 1950 (Box 504, Folder 3375)
    - Norway - Humanities and Arts, 1950; 1950/767.R
      - Norway, 1950 (Box 504, Folder 3375)
  - Iran, 1950; 1950/771
    - Iran, 1950 (Box 505, Folder 3376)
    - Iran - Medical Sciences, 1950; 1950/771.A
      - Iran, 1950 (Box 505, Folder 3377)
  - Portugal, 1950; 1950/773
    - Portugal, 1950 (Box 505, Folder 3378)
  - Romania, 1950; 1950/783
    - Romania, 1950 (Box 505, Folder 3378)
  - USSR, 1950; 1950/785
    - USSR, 1950 (Box 505, Folder 3378)
  - Latvia, 1950; 1950/786
    - Latvia, 1950 (Box 505, Folder 3378)
  - Finland, 1950; 1950/787
    - Finland, 1950 (Box 505, Folder 3378)
    - Finland - Nursing, 1950; 1950/787.C
      - Finland, 1950 (Box 505, Folder 3378)
    - Finland - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1950; 1950/787.E
      - Finland, 1950 (Box 505, Folder 3378)
  - Poland, 1950; 1950/789
    - Poland, 1950 (Box 505, Folder 3379)
    - Poland - Medical Sciences, 1950; 1950/789.A
      - Poland, 1950 (Box 505, Folder 3379)
    - Poland - Nursing, 1950; 1950/789.C
      - Poland, 1950 (Box 505, Folder 3379)
  - Spain, 1950; 1950/795
    - Spain, 1950 (Box 505, Folder 3379)
    - Spain - Medical Sciences, 1950; 1950/795.A